{
  "number" : 15,
  "0" : {
    "problem": "65 + 5",
    "answer": 70
  },
  "1" : {
    "problem": "2 + 2",
    "answer": 4
  },
  "2" : {
    "problem": "7 * 4",
    "answer": 28
  },
  "3" : {
    "problem": "8 - 2",
    "answer": 6
  },
  "4" : {
    "problem": "32 - 10",
    "answer": 22
  },
  "5" : {
    "problem": "2 * 3",
    "answer": 6
  },
  "6" : {
    "problem": "9 / 3",
    "answer": 3
  },
  "7" : {
    "problem": "14 / 7",
    "answer": 2
  },
  "8" : {
    "problem": "245 - 41",
    "answer": 204
  },
  "9" : {
    "problem": "5 * 6",
    "answer": 30
  },
  "10" : {
    "problem": "7 - 8",
    "answer": -1
  },
  "11" : {
    "problem": "3 * 4",
    "answer": 12
  },
  "12" : {
    "problem": "5 + 5 + 5",
    "answer": 15
  },
  "13" : {
    "problem": "45 / 5",
    "answer": 9
  },
  "14" : {
    "problem": "34 + 4",
    "answer": 38
  }
}